

#### About

Currently open for new opportunities as UX Designer, UX/UI Designer I am an enthusiastic and dedicated professional with a solid academic background in Human-Computer Interaction and Design, Research and Computer Science. I am passionate by user experience design, user interface design, user research, web development and new technologies.

# Core expertise

- · Design Thinking workshops
- User Research
- User Testing
- Prototyping
- Design Systems

#### Tools

- Adobe Suite
- Figma
- FigJam
- Miro

# Soft skills

- Communication
- Flexibility
- · Time management
- · Problem-solving mindset
- · Team spirit
- Positivity

# Languages

English (Bilingual)
French (Proficient)
Arabic (Native)
Spanish (Notions)
Hungarian (Notions)

# Yassine Ben Lakhdhar

UX/UI designer 🦄

Portfolio LinkedIn

(+33) 6 27 49 25 49 yblakhdhar@gmail.com Paris 75013

Immediately available Geographic mobility

### Work experience

Since 12/2023 (Paris, France)

**UX/UI Designer, Incenteev** 

As a UX/UI Designer, I'm responsible for :

- · Understanding user needs and transforming these insights into innovative solutions,
- · Designing attractive and functional user interfaces,
- · Creating new components and improving the design system,
- · Designing several AI features in collaboration with the head of engineering.

12/2021 - 12/2022 (Paris, France)

#### **UX Designer, Ubisoft Entertainment**

In this world-leading video game company, I have as a UX Designer at the Online Services division:

- Actively collaborated within a team of 15 UX and UI designers applying best practices in user experience design and on the application of a Design System to online services applications,
- Assisted the maintenance of the game statistics application in the Ubisoft Connect platform, exposing specific and engaging stats per game for more than 150 million players online on Mobile, PC and Console,
- Proposed an improved user experience on how Ubisoft Store reduction coupons are granted internally at
   Ubisoft, impacting +20K collaborators worldwide along with a UI designer, and Project Manager,
- Performed user interviews, user tests, and prototype of a User Account linking solution, successfully
  converting over 2 million players to claim Ubisoft in-game rewards and fresh content on all their gaming
  platforms using their Amazon Prime subscriptions.

03/2021 - 08/2021 (Paris, France)

# Interaction & Experience Design Research Intern, <u>Ex(situ - LISN Research Lab - INRIA Saclay</u>

As a researcher at ex)situ research lab, I was able to explore human-computer interaction and interaction design research, specifically how dance practitioners document their work:

 Collaborated alongside a choreographer and design researcher, designed and developed an interactive web-based mobile-first application used by several dancers and choreographers in Paris.

09/2019 - 01/2020 (Debrecen, Hungary)

#### **Customer Support Agent, Ryanair**

In this company that is Europe's largest airline, I have had the following experience:

 Treatment of customers needs and requests over calls and live chat, which helped my understanding on the importance of keeping track and measure customer success and customer churn at the customer support level at the online division to propose the best solutions.

## Education

12/2021 - 10/2022 (Paris, France)

Web Design, Ecole Webstart

09/2020 - 09/2021 (Paris, France)

Computer Science MSc, Institut Polytechnique de Paris

09/2016 - 06/2020 (Debrecen, Hungary)

Computer Science BSc, <u>University of Debrecen</u>

09/2014 - 06/2016 (Cambridge, UK)

Cambridge A levels, Cambridge International